Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1949-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 1: Administrative records, 1949-2007 (Boxes 1-196)
  - Subseries 1.5: Communications and Events, 1950-2006
    - Sub-subseries 1.5.3: Printed material, 1950-2006
      - Tales from the Vienna Woods reviews, 1978 (Box 186, Folder 3)
      - Tartuffe reviews, 1985 (Box 186, Folder 4)
      - Tech department press mentions, 1967-1971 (Box 186, Folder 5)
      - Teibele and Her Demon reviews, 1979 (Box 186, Folder 6)
      - The Tempest reviews, 1984 (Box 186, Folder 7)
      - The Tenth Man reviews, 1968 (Box 186, Folder 8)
      - Theatre Arts "Old Vat" article, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 9)
      - Thief reviews, 1981 (Box 186, Folder 10)
      - Three Men on a Horse reviews, 1952-1953 (Box 186, Folder 11)
      - Three Men on a Horse reviews, 1973-1974 (Box 186, Folder 12)
      - Three One Acts reviews, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 13)
      - Three short plays, 1961 (Box 186, Folder 14)
      - Three Sisters reviews, 1984 (Box 186, Folder 15)
      - The Threepenny Opera reviews, 1963-1964 (Box 186, Folder 16)
      - Tiger at the Gates reviews, 1961 (Box 186, Folder 17)
      - The Time of Your Life reviews, 1962 (Box 186, Folder 18)
      - Tintypes reviews, 1979 (Box 186, Folder 19)
      - Tom reviews, 1974 (Box 186, Folder 20)
      - Tomfoolery reviews, 1982 (Box 186, Folder 21)
      - The Tot Family reviews, 1976 (Box 186, Folder 22)
      - Tricks reviews, 1972 (Box 186, Folder 23)
      - Trinidad Sisters invitation and reviews, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 24)
      - Twelfth Night reviews, 1951 (Box 186, Folder 25)
      - Twelfth Night reviews, 1971-1972 (Box 187, Folder 1)
      - Twelve Angry Men reviews, 1963 (Box 187, Folder 2)
      - Two Plays (double bill) reviews, 1961 (Box 187, Folder 3)
      - Two plays by Samuel Beckett reviews, 1973 (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Two Gentlemen of Verona reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 5)
      - Uncle Vanya reviews, 1962 (Box 187, Folder 6)
      - Under Milk Wood reviews, 1962 (Box 187, Folder 7)
      - Undiscovered Country reviews, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 8)
      - Uptight reviews, 1972 (Box 187, Folder 9)
      - Vivisections from the Blown Mind reviews, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 10)
      - Volpone reviews, 1962-1963 (Box 187, Folder 11)
      - Waiting for Godot reviews, 1976 (Box 187, Folder 12)
      - A Walk in the Woods reviews, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 13)
      - The Wall articles and reviews, 1964 (Box 187, Folder 14)
      - "Washington Battles that 'Hick' label" article, 1960 (Box 187, Folder 15)
      - What the Butler Saw reviews, 1971 (Box 187, Folder 16)
      - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf reviews, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 17)
      - The Wild Duck reviews, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 18)
      - The Winter's Tale reviews, 1979 (Box 187, Folder 19)
      - Wipe-Out Games reviews, 1971 (Box 187, Folder 20)
      - Women and Water reviews, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 21)
      - Woza Albert reviews, 1984 (Box 187, Folder 22)
      - Woza Albert reviews, 1984 (Box 187, Folder 23)
      - You Can't Take it With You reviews, 1969 (Box 187, Folder 24)
      - You Can't Take it With You reviews, 1979-1980 (Box 187, Folder 25)
      - Zalmen or the Madness of God reviews, film, 1974-1975 (Box 187, Folder 26)
      - Zalmen or the Madness of God reviews, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 27)
    - Sub-subseries 1.5.4: Theater Communications Group, 1960-1994
      Sub-subseries 4: Theater Communications Group contains correspondence, reports, and other information generated from Arena's association with the Theater Communications Group.
      - Theater Communications Group, May 16, 1994 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Theater Communications Group Annual Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Theater Communications Group annual report, letters, press releases, and information for playwrights, 1974-1975 (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - Theater Communications Group Board, 1976-1983 (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Theater Communications Group budget and salary information, 1982-1983 (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Theater Communications Group conference, 1994 (Box 188, Folder 6)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 188, Folder 8)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence, 1964 (Box 188, Folder 9)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence, 1965 (Box 188, Folder 10)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence, 1966 (Box 188, Folder 11)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence, 1967 (Box 188, Folder 12)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence, 1968 (Box 188, Folder 13)
      - Theater Communications Group correspondence travel, 1966-1967 (Box 188, Folder 14)
      - Theater Communications Group general file (1 of 3), 1980-1982 (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Theater Communications Group general file (2 of 3), 1974-1980 (Box 189, Folder 2)
      - Theater Communications Group general file (3 of 3), 1963-1975 (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Theater Communications Group Hispanic translation project, 1984 (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - Theater Communications Group letters, 1963, 1966 (Box 189, Folder 5)
      - Theater Communications Group Manager's Bulletin, 1977-1985 (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Theater Communications Group memos, letters, meeting information, 1974-1983 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Theater Communications Group miscellaneous materials, 1961-1963 (Box 189, Folder 8)
      - Theater Communications Group reports, 1965 (Box 189, Folder 9)
      - Theater Communications Group reports, 1965-1967 (Box 189, Folder 10)
      - Theater Communications Group TABS, 1968-1973 (Box 190, Folder 1)
      - Theater Communications Group telephone proposals and costs, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - Theater Communications Group cable television and performing arts, 1968-1981 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Theater Communications Group theater study for Congress, 1976 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - Theater Communications Group theatre development fund, 1972-1979 (Box 190, Folder 5)
      - Theater Communications Group theater directories/newsletters, 1977-1984 (Box 190, Folder 6)
      - Theater Communications Group theatre rentals, 1966-1978 (Box 190, Folder 7)
      - Theater Communications Group three institutions, 1973-1980 (Box 190, Folder 8)
      - Theater Communications Group three institutions bill, 1978-1980 (Box 190, Folder 9)
      - Theater Communications Group three institutions narrative descriptions and proposal for maintenance support, 1980 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - Theater Communications Group three institutions proposal and legislation, 1980 (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1.6: Buildings and facilities, 1949-1995
    This subseries includes information about and architectural plans for Arena's various buildings over the years.
    - SS Potomac log, 1949 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Hippodrome-Occupancy Permit Application, 1949-1950 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - The Old Vat (mortgage other plans and projects), 1956-1959 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Birth of a Theatre by Joseph R. Judge (building history), 1958 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Arena's search for a new building news article, 1959 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - S.W. Arena History/Letters to Harry Weese from Zelda, 1959 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Harry Wise (architect) correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - new building potential contractor correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Old Vat move news articles, 1959-1961 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - building-related history, articles on History of Arena Stage, 1950s-1960s (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Early Building History, 1960s-1970s (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - Announcement of new building plans reception, 1960 (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - The New Permanent Theatre Home of Washington's own Arena Stage brochure, 1960 (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - Addendum No 1 to architectural plans (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - Addendum No 1 to architectural plans (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 191, Folder 15)
    - Construction Correspondence, DC government, 1959-1960 (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - Change Order Bulletin No 1 and 2-architects and engineers, 1960 (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - Century Lighting Inc, specifications Arena Stage, 1960 (Box 191, Folder 18)
    - Harry Weese correspondence (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Harry Weese (architect) correspondence (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - New building correspondence, 1960 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - New building correspondence, specifications, 1960 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Specifications for combined building trades, mechanical trades, electrical trades for the construction of Arena Stage, 1960 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - S.W. Arena History (building), 1960-1961 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - construction, mortgage, building-related finances, 1960-1962 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - John Tester and Son Contract, negotiations and payment, 1960-1962 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Theatre Architecture, 1960s-1970s (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - New building correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Building-related and general History of Arena Stage, 1961-1973 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Harry Weese architects correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Harry Weese architects bills and drawings, 1962 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - H. Weese architect, correspondence, financial, 1962 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Harry Weese, architect, correspondence, 1963 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Program Arena II, Harry Weese, early 1960s (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Arena II - landscaping costs, early 1960s (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Arena II Parking Lot - estimates and plans, 1962 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Westinghouse Air Conditioning, 1962 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Arena Stage building, 1961-1970 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Stage Lighting, 1964 (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Honor Awards for Design Excellence, 1966 (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - To Build a Theatre by Zelda Fichandler, 1967 (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Drawings for building addition, late 1960s (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - Korean National Theatre, Seoul, 1967 (Box 193, Folder 16)
    - Kreeger addition - Washington Drama Society, Inc, 1967-1983 (Box 193, Folder 17)
    - Arena II - cost estimates, 1967-1968 (Box 193, Folder 18)
    - Arena II - Architect's bids, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Arena II bids, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Arena II bids-comparison contractor, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Arena II bids - Crough, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Arena II - design ideas and equipment, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Arena II Redevelopment Land Agency Hearing record and lease, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Kreeger Theater news articles, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Arena II - Edward Crough, Contractor, 1968-1969 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Contractor E. M. Crough correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Kreeger Building background information, architectural drawings, publicity, 1968-1970 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Stage II press kit, Kreeger information, 1968-1970 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Arena II - Heffron, subcontractor, 1969 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Stage II construction, 1969 (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Arena II - contractor and architect's invoices, correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Arena II architect and contractor correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - Arena II architect and contractor correspondence, 1970 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Arena II carpets, 1970 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Kreeger Theater background press material, 1970 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Kreeger Theater opening news articles, 1970 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Redevelopment Land Agency - annual report, 1970 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Notice of Public Hearing for Metro Alignment, October 12, 1971 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Woodward Manufacturing Co. correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Maintenance expenditures, actual and projected, 1979-1980 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Arena II (Kreeger) Financial Information and land development, 1978-1985 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Application of The Arena Stage for designation as an historical landmark, 1980 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Application of The Arena Stage for the designation as an historical landmark appendices, 1980 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Historical Site Hearing, 1980 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Historic site Application result, related material, 1970s-1983 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Acquisition of Arena Stage, 1985 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Kreeger Land Purchase, 1985 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Box Office Renovation, 1994-1995 (Box 196, Folder 3)
- Series 2: Production files, 1950-2010 (Boxes 197-588, 654-663)
  This series is comprised of records related to the artistic development and performance of Arena's plays.
  - Subseries 2.1: Dramaturgical files, 1958-2010
    This subseries documents literary, historical and background research done by Arena's literary department for various plays.
    - African Company Study Guides, 1992-1993 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Agamemnon and His Daughters (final), 2001-2002 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Agamemnon and His Daughters (final draft), 2001-2002 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Agamemnon and His Daughters (rehearsal draft), 2001-2002 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Agamemnon and His Daughters (first draft), 2001-2002 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Agamemnon and His Daughters (second draft), 2001-2002 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Airplane Construction, Undated (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - (All My Sons) Arthur Miller, circa 1999-2000 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - All My Sons Previews, Undated (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - AMS Wright Scandal, circa 1999-2000 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - All My Sons - Returning Vets, Undated (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - All My Sons - History 1947, Undated (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - All My Sons (1 of 2), Undated (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - All My Sons (2 of 2), Undated (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - All My Sons Research, Undated (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - All My Sons Packet, Undated (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - All My Sons (1 of 2), Undated (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - All My Sons (2 of 2), Undated (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - All My Sons Sundries, Undated (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - All My Sons Profiteering, Undated (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - All My Sons - Various Army Facts, Undated (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - All My Sons (1 of 2), Undated (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - All My Sons (2 of 2), Undated (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Almost Blue Script and Notes, Undated (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Alonzo Lamont's Life Go Boom! - Final Arena Draft, 1994 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Alonzo Lamont's Life Go Boom! - Preliminary Research, Undated (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - An American Daughter, 2002-2003 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - An American Daughter - Script, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - An American Daughter - All Changes: Cuts, additions, rewrites, etc, 2002-2003 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - A History of the American Film, 1977 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Animal Crackers Scripts (1 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Animal Crackers Scripts (2 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Animal Crackers Scripts (3 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Animal Crackers Misc. Notes and Info, Undated (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Animal Crackers Scripts and Research (1 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Animal Crackers Scripts and Research (2 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Animal Crackers Scripts and Research (3 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Animal Crackers Scripts and Research (4 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Anna in the Tropics Actor's Packet, 2004 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Anna Christie Actor's Packet (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Anna Christie Actor's Packet (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Anna Christie Actor's Packet (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Anthems Drafts (1 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Anthems Drafts (2 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Anthems Drafts (3 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Anthems Drafts (4 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Anthems Drafts (5 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Anthems Drafts (6 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Anthems Drafts (7 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Anthems Drafts (8 of 8), 2002-2003 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Arcadia (1 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Arcadia (2 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Arcadia (3 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Arcadia (4 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Arcadia Dress Rehearsal Photos, 1996-1997 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Arcadia Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Arcadia Study Guide Materials (1 of 3), Fall 1996 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Arcadia Study Guide Materials (2 of 3), Fall 1996 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Arcadia Study Guide Materials (3 of 3), Fall 1996 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - The Art of Thornton Wilder by Malcolm Goldstein, Undated (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Arthur Miller Festival Actor's Research Packet, 2006 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Arthur Miller Festival Research Packet (1 of 3), 2006-2007 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Arthur Miller Festival Research Packet (2 of 3), 2006-2007 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Arthur Miller Festival Research Packet (3 of 3), 2006-2007 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - The As If Body Loop Script, 2005 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - At the River I Stand - Video - Memphis, 1969 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - August Wilson Research, Undated (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Awake and Sing! Actor's Packet, Undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Battle of Angels, Undated (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Battle of Angels - Produced First, Undated (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Billy Bishop Goes to War Actor's Packet, Undated (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Black No More Notes and Guides, 1998 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Black No More Notes and Guides, 1996-1998 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Black No More Notes and Guides, 1998 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Black No More Script Drafts (1 of 7), 1996-1998 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Black No More Script Drafts (2 of 7), 1996-1998 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Black No More Script Drafts (3 of 7), 1996-1998 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Black No More Script Drafts (4 of 7), 1996-1998 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Black No More Script Drafts (5 of 7), 1996-1998 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Black No More Script Drafts (6 of 7), 1996-1998 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Black No More Script Drafts (7 of 7), 1996-1998 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Blithe Spirit (1 of 4), Undated (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Blithe Spirit (2 of 4), Undated (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Blithe Spirit (3 of 4), Undated (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Blithe Spirit (4 of 4), Undated (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Blithe Spirit - Noel Coward - Dramaturgy File (1 of 7), April-June, 1996 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Blithe Spirit - Noel Coward - Dramaturgy File (2 of 7), April-June, 1996 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Blithe Spirit - Noel Coward - Dramaturgy File (3 of 7), April-June, 1996 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Blithe Spirit - Noel Coward - Dramaturgy File (4 of 7), April-June, 1996 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Blithe Spirit - Noel Coward - Dramaturgy File (5 of 7), April-June, 1996 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Blithe Spirit - Noel Coward - Dramaturgy File (6 of 7), April-June, 1996 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Blithe Spirit - Noel Coward - Dramaturgy File (7 of 7), April-June, 1996 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Blood Knot - Product "A" Script, Undated (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Blood Knot Study Guide, Undated (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Blue (1 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Blue (2 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Blue (3 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Blue (4 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Blue (5 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Blue (6 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Blue (7 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Blue (8 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Blue (9 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Blue (10 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Blue (11 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Blue (12 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Blue (13 of 13), 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Blues for an Alabama Sky (1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Blues for an Alabama Sky (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Book of Days Dramaturgy Resource Book (1 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Book of Days Dramaturgy Resource Book (2 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Book of Days Dramaturgy Resource Book (3 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Book of Days Dramaturgy Resource Book (4 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Book of Days, Undated (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Book of Days, Undated (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Born Guilty Background Materials, Undated (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Born Guilty Production Materials, June 26, 1990 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Born Guilty Production Materials, Undated (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Born Guilty Production Materials, Undated (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Born Guilty Background Materials, Undated (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Born Guilty, Undated (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Born Guilty by Peter Sichrovsky - Master Copy, 1988 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Cabaret Master Articles (1 of 3), 2006 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Cabaret Master Articles (2 of 3), 2006 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Cabaret Master Articles (3 of 3), 2006 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - The Arena Companion to Cabaret (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - The Arena Companion to Cabaret (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Cabaret Research (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Cabaret Research (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Camelot, Undated (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Candide (1 of 3), Undated (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Candide (2 of 3), Undated (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Candide (3 of 3), Undated (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Candide Reviews, Undated (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Candide Post-Show Cheat Sheet, Undated (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Carmen, Undated (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee Williams Cat [on a Hot Tin Roof], Undated (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof Research, 1998-1999 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Checkmates and Cleveland Reviews, Undated (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Chorus of Disapproval, December 30, 1988-February 5, 1989 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Carol 1941 (1 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Christmas Carol 1941 (2 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Christmas Carol 1941 Actor's Packet (Copy 1) (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Carol 1941 Actor's Packet (Copy 1) (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Christmas Carol 1941 Actor's Packet (Copy 2) (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Carol 1941 Actor's Packet (Copy 2) (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Christmas Carol 1941 Notes for Actor's Packet, October 2007 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - The Clean House by Sarah Ruhl, circa 2000s (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - The Cocoanuts Scripts and Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - The Comedy of Manners, Undated (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Coming of the Hurricane (1 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Coming of the Hurricane (2 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Coming of the Hurricane (3 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Coming of the Hurricane Articles, 1995-1996 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Coming of the Hurricane Reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Coming of the Hurricane Script, 1995-1996 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Coming of the Hurricane Study Guide, 1995-1996 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Common Ground, circa 1992 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Common Ground adapted by Bill Cain, circa 1992 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Common Ground Notes, circa 1992 (Box 215, Folder 6)